<resources>
    <string name="app_name">exer2_Palicpic_B4L</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="question">Which Disney Princess are you?</string>
    <string name="start_text">Click Start!</string>
    <string name="anna_bio">You are
        \n<b>Princess Anna</b>
        \n Anna is more daring than graceful and, at times, can act before she thinks.
        But she\'s also the most optimistic and caring person you\'ll ever meet. She longs to
        reconnect with her sister Elsa, as they were close during their childhood. When Elsa
        accidentally unleashes a magical secret that locks the kingdom of Arendelle in an eternal winter,
        Anna embarks on a dangerous adventure to make things right. Armed with only her fearlessness,
        a never-give-up attitude and her faith in others, Anna is determined to save both her kingdom and her family.
        \n\n\nhttps://disney.fandom.com/wiki/Anna</string>
    <string name="ariel_bio">You are
        \n<b>Princess Ariel</b>
         \n Ariel is an independent, headstrong and determined young mermaid. She is the youngest
        and prettiest princess of the sea but spends most of her time outside the palace walls of
        Atlantica singing, daydreaming, and adventuring with her best friend Flounder the guppy fish,
        and sometimes Sebastian the crab who is also the royal adviser to Ariel\'s father. At the age
        of 16, she unexpectedly becomes deeply infatuated with a young and handsome human prince named
        Eric and sacrifices all things dear to her for the chance of being with her one true love.
        \n\n\nhttps://disney.fandom.com/wiki/Ariel</string>
    <string name="aurora_bio">You are
        \n<b>Princess Aurora</b>
        \n Aurora is gentle and loving, and is raised by three fairies named Flora, Fauna, and Merryweather.
        She lives in the forest, where she meets the Prince, her one true love.
        \n\n\nhttps://disney.fandom.com/wiki/Aurora</string>
    <string name="belle_bio">You are
        \n<b>Princess Belle</b>
        \n Far-off places, daring sword fights, a prince in disguise, Belle longs for so much more than a "normal life"
        in this small, provincial town - a town where girls don\'t aspire to more than marrying well. Still, adventure
        is the last thing on her mind when she rides her horse, Philippe, into the forest to find her beloved father,
        who is missing. Thinking only of her father, she makes a bargain with a Beast who holds her father captive in his castle.
        Though the Beast now holds the key to Belle\'s prison, he doesn\'t have the key to her heart, and her yearning spirit
        won\'t be kept prisoner. But after he risks his own life to save hers, she begins to see past his appearance.
        She realizes that deep inside him there might be something more than she - or he - has ever dreamed.
        \n\n\nhttps://disney.fandom.com/wiki/Belle</string>
    <string name="cinderella_bio">You are
        \n<b>Princess Cinderella</b>
        \n Cinderella is kind to all, especially her mice friends, Jaq and Gus. She has faith that if you keep on believing,
        your wish will come true. With help from her fairy godmother, she gets a chance to live her dreams.
        \n\n\nhttps://disney.fandom.com/wiki/Cinderella_(character)</string>
    <string name="elsa_bio">You are
        \n<b>Princess Elsa</b>
        \n From the outside, Elsa looks poised, regal, and reserved, but in reality, she lives in fear as she wrestles with a mighty secret
        - she was born with the power to create ice and snow. It\'s a beautiful ability, but also extremely dangerous. Haunted by the moment
        her magic nearly killed her younger sister Anna, Elsa has isolated herself, spending every waking minute trying to suppress her growing
        powers. Her mounting emotions trigger the magic, accidentally setting off an eternal winter that she can\'t stop. She fears she\'s
        becoming a monster and that no one, not even her sister, can help her.
        \n\n\nhttps://disney.fandom.com/wiki/Elsa</string>
    <string name="jasmine_bio">You are
        \n<b>Princess Jasmine</b>
        \n Jasmine is a dreamer who loves her pet tiger, Rajah. She\'s free-spirited, confident, and kind. When she meets Aladdin,
        she discovers the wonders she\'s often imagined outside the palace walls.
        \n\n\nhttps://disney.fandom.com/wiki/Jasmine</string>
    <string name="moana_bio">You are
        \n<b>Princess Moana</b>
        \n Moana is the vibrant, tenacious and optimistic daughter of the Chief of Motunui,
        thriving on her island but drawn to the ocean. When her island is threatened by a dark force,
        Moana sets sail outside the reef and her comfort zone to right a wrong, save her people, and
        find the answers she\'s been searching for her whole life.
        \n\n\nhttps://disney.fandom.com/wiki/Moana_(character)</string>
    <string name="mulan_bio">You are
        \n<b>Mulan</b>
        \n Fa Mulan is the titular protagonist of Disney\'s 1998 animated feature film of the same name. She is the strong-willed
        and tenacious daughter of a war veteran, who strives to uphold her family\'s honor. When her father is called back into battle
        to defend China from Shan Yu, Mulan opts to protect him by taking his place under the guise of a male soldier named Ping.
        \n\n\nhttps://disney.fandom.com/wiki/Fa_Mulan</string>
    <string name="rapunzel_bio">You are
        \n<b>Princess Rapunzel</b>
        \n Rapunzel may have lived her entire life locked inside a hidden tower, but Rapunzel is no damsel in distress.
        The girl with the 70 feet of golden hair is an energetic, inquisitive teenager who fills her days with art, books,
        and imagination. Rapunzel is full of curiosity about the outside world, and she can\'t help but feel that her true destiny
        lies outside of the lonely tower walls. Rapunzel has always obeyed Mother Gothel by staying hidden away and keeping her
        magical hair a secret but with her 18th birthday just a day away, she is fed up with her sheltered life and ready for
        adventure. When a charming thief seeks refuge in her tower, Rapunzel defies Gothel and seizes the opportunity to
        answer the call of the kingdom. With the unwilling Flynn Rider along for the journey, Rapunzel leaves the tower for
        the first time, and begins a hilarious, hair-raising journey that will untangle many secrets along the way.
        \n\n\nhttps://disney.fandom.com/wiki/Rapunzel</string>
    <string name="snowwhite_bio">You are
        \n<b>Princess Snow White</b>
        \n Snow White was born into the royal family. Her mother died shortly after her birth. After some time, Snow White\'s father
        remarried a vain and cold-hearted queen. Not long after their marriage, the King, Snow White\'s beloved father, suspiciously died,
        leaving the young princess as an orphan.
        \n\n\nhttps://disney.fandom.com/wiki/Snow_White</string>
    <string name="tiana_bio">You are
        \n<b>Princess Tiana</b>
        \n Tiana dreams of opening her own restaurant. She works hard to try and make that dream come true.
        In a twist of fate, she kisses a frog and goes on an adventure through the New Orleans bayou.
        \n\n\nhttps://disney.fandom.com/wiki/Tiana</string>
</resources>
